Guide to the
Brown University Library
- MNGW Please Read Me First.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Date created: 2012-07-09 11:58:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-09 12:02:58 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 1 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 1 Gender Aptitude/Date created: 2012-07-01 15:12:35 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-05 19:20:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- THE Acknowledgments.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Date created: 2011-10-15 10:53:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-11-07 14:27:45 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My Gender Workbook/Chapter Drafts in Pages format/Date created: 2012-02-04 17:42:35 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-09 13:47:21 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB Meds Mar 2013.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/KB Meds/Meds Nov 2012/Date created: 2013-03-03 20:38:14 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-03-03 20:38:33 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dixie Belle Reader 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Letters to Tom/Date created: 2011-06-27 22:35:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-27 23:04:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb_medical_history_2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2010-07-15 20:22:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-07-15 20:30:18 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 6 KB Edit Chap 6.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-17 13:37:31 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-17 16:13:03 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Sync.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Femme Conf Keynote/Date created: 2010-08-25 22:30:00 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-26 00:28:11 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 5 Sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 5 There's Only One Gender—Yours/Date created: 2012-06-30 04:34:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 04:35:17 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MyGenderWorkbook Update Thoughts.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Old Workbook Files/Date created: 2011-12-14 17:54:40 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-12-14 18:10:57 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Antig-Lines.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Transtigone/Date created: 2010-04-11 13:23:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-04-11 13:23:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Queer Pleasant Book Cover Beta 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Layout & Design/QueerPleasantCover ƒ/Date created: 2011-05-24 13:09:55 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-24 14:06:58 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Hidden A Gender.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/theatrical pieces/Date created: 2010-10-04 01:44:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-04 01:44:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-5 Girl.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/8/7/1/Attachments/178092/2/Date created: 2017-01-15 23:55:42 EST-0500Date modified: 2017-01-15 23:55:42 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Sex, Bullies, and You 2009.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2009-02-25 00:23:41 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-25 08:09:08 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB Photo Assortment 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Bios-KB/Date created: 2011-04-29 14:21:25 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-22 17:11:25 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Supplies.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Archive Project/Date created: 2011-05-23 13:41:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-23 13:41:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- email from pussy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2012-08-22 23:05:05 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-22 23:05:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 4 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 4 Let Why = Why/Date created: 2012-05-26 11:06:35 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-02 13:43:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Put with Pyramid.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Date created: 2012-05-11 17:35:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-12 15:06:34 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Final.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Femme Conf Keynote/Date created: 2010-08-20 20:00:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-21 01:11:46 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Miss G monologue.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/scripts/Virtually Yours ƒ/Date created: 2011-05-22 16:42:17 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-22 16:47:56 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- She-MaleRisingShawnaVirago.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-01-17 21:18:55 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-17 21:18:55 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Chelsea Manning Open Letter To.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Chelsea Manning Open Letter/Date created: 2013-08-24 17:14:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-24 18:10:15 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Virtually Yours 2.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/scripts/Virtually Yours ƒ/Date created: 2011-05-22 17:34:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-22 17:34:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 7.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 7 Get Ready To Do Your Gender/Date created: 2012-04-03 17:46:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-04 22:30:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 1_sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 1 Gender Aptitude/Date created: 2012-06-29 18:22:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-29 18:24:04 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 10-11 newsletter.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Newsletters/2010-2011 Newsletter Folder/Date created: 2010-09-11 18:47:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-09-13 01:25:30 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- FINAL Schedule for Kate Bornstein Visit.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Date created: 2012-04-12 14:27:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-12 14:27:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- NWGW_Tweets from HG Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Date created: 2012-06-30 17:53:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-01 12:38:26 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- cover letter to page proof corrections.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Notes on QPD Page Proofs/Date created: 2011-12-05 11:02:30 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-12-05 11:34:14 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW As to copy editor Qs January 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Copy Edits/Date created: 2013-01-02 12:20:39 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-02 14:02:04 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Acceptance Speech KESHET 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Date created: 2009-03-28 12:15:59 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-28 15:21:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Pioneer Speaking.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2014-06-02 14:39:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2014-06-02 14:39:21 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 2 sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 2 Where Is Gender?/Date created: 2012-06-29 22:02:34 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-29 22:04:11 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- femme on femme long version.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Elaina Ellis/Date created: 2008-11-20 13:58:08 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-08-31 22:17:56 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- memoir-template.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2013-11-08 17:18:36 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-11-08 17:18:36 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Mitzvah Sabbath KESHET 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Tao of Sabbath Mitvah Boddhisatva ƒ/Date created: 2009-03-28 16:42:07 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-28 17:16:09 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Appearance Agreement Kate Bornstein.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/U IL Champaign Urbana/Date created: 2009-10-28 20:22:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-10-28 20:27:16 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages